Finding aid to the Classes of 1879-1890 records CA.MS.01023
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1882 Records, 1879-2000; 7 boxes (2 linear feet)
  - Class of 1882: Craig, Jean Maria (Box 1393, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1882: Daniels, Mary Bryant (General), 1904-05 (Box 1393, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1882: Daniels, Mary Bryant (Photographs) (Box 1393, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1882: Eastman, Maria Rebecca, undated (Box 1393, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1882: Eppendorf, Lina, 1945 (Box 1393, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1882: Fitch, Laura Forbes, 1914-15; 1918; 1926 (Box 1393, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1882: Gardner, Ada Grant (Box 1393, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1882: Girdler, Lydia Louise (Box 1393, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1882: Goodell, May Evelyn (Box 1393, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1882: Goodwin, Clara Kenrick (Box 1393, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1882: Greene, Grace Miller, 1929; 1931; 1940-41; 1948-49 (Box 1393, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1882: Gulliver, Mary, 1922; 1934 (Box 1393, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1882: Gulliver, Mary (Album), 1878-1882 (Box 1398.1)
  - Class of 1882: Hammond, Mary Grace, 1911; 1914 (Box 1393, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1882: Hayes, Clara Louise (Box 1393, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1882: Hidden, Mary Belle (Box 1393, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1882: Huggins, Mary Augusta, 1884; 1916; 1923 (Box 1393, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1882: Hungerford, Caroline Marsh (Box 1393, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1882: Jackson, Annie Brown (Letters), 1881; 1888-89 (Box 1393, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1882: Jackson, Annie Brown (Photographs), 1889; 1892; 1916; 1919; 1921; 1923-24 (Box 1393, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1882: Jackson, Annie Brown ("Mediaeval France and the Troubadours") (Box 1393, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1882: Jackson, Annie (Scrapbook) (Box 1398.4)
  - Class of 1882: Jameson, Mary, 1930 (Box 1393, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1882: Kellogg, Sarah Delano (Box 1393, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1882: King, Fanny (Box 1393, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Nellie Rose, 2000 (Box 1393, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence: Jan-Jun, typed copies), 1880-1881 (Box 1397, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence: Sept-Dec, typed copies), 1881 (Box 1397, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence: Jan-Jun, typed copies) (Box 1397, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence: Jan-Jun, originals), 1880-1881 (Box 1397, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence: Sept-Dec, originals), 1881 (Box 1397, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence: Jan-Jun, originals) (Box 1397, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Correspondence), 1909-1949 (Box 1397, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor, 1904 (Box 1397, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1882: Larrison, Eleanor (Photographs) (Box 1397, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1882: Lester, Grace Darling (Box 1394, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1882: Luck, Emma Josephine (Box 1394, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1882: McClellan, Katherine Elizabeth (Box 1394, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1882: McKee, Isabel Dinwiddie, 1914 (Box 1394, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1882: McKeown, Ella Maranda (Box 1394, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1882: Merriam, Florence B., 1980 (Box 1394, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1882: Milligan, Josephine Ewing, 1922 (Box 1394, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1882: Mix, Mary Jacob (Box 1394, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1882: Palmer, Lucy White, undated (Box 1394, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1882: Palmes, Nannie Gertrude, 1878-80; 1890 (Box 1394, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1882: Peabody, Susan Perkins (Box 1394, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1882: Pellett, Frances (Box 1394, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1882: Pellett, Frances (Photographs) (Box 1398, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1882: Pellett, Frances (Scrapbook), Early-Mid 1880s (Box 1398)
  - Class of 1882: Peirce, Annie Calder, 1876; 1878-79; 1906 (Box 1394, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1882: Peloubet, Mary Alice, 1902 (Box 1394, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1882: Pettibone, Mary Cordelia, 1880-82 (Box 1394, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1882: Phillips, Nella Sumner, 1879 (Box 1394, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1882: Preston, Grace Alma (Box 1394, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1882: Safford, Helen, 1880 (Box 1394, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1882: Smith, Clara Janet Augusta, 1921 (Box 1394, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1882: Smith, Theodate Louise (General), 1898; 1912; 1914 (Box 1394, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1882: Smith, Theodate Louise (Writings), 1904; 1911-14 (Box 1394, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1882: Snell, Harriet Margaret, undated (Box 1394, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1882: Soule, Haidee Hobart, 1889 (Box 1394, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1882: Tenney, Mary Alice, 1912; 1916; 1920-22; 1925; 1934 (Box 1394, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1882: Tucker, Alice Elizabeth (Box 1394, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1882: Vinton, Maria Mitchell, 1899; 1912-14; 1916 (Box 1394, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1882: Washburn, Clara Spencer (Box 1394, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1882: Watson, Esther Josephine (Box 1394, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1882: Wright, Elizabeth Boleyn, 1894 (Box 1394, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1882: Unidentified (Album) (Box 1398.2, Box 1398.3)
- Class of 1883 Records, 1875-1998; 16 boxes (6.75 linear feet)
  The Class of 1883 was the fifth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1883 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1883. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, correspondence, cards, memorabilia, scrapbooks, journals, albums, student's notes and work, newspaper clippings, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1883.
  - Class of 1883: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1400, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Commencement (Box 1400, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Commencement Speaker (Box 1400, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Commencement Music (Box 1400, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Photograph List (Box 1400, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Elm, 1889; 1915; 1917-21 (Box 1400, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Class-German (Box 1400, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: History, 1881-83; 1936-37 (Box 1400, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Peacocks, 1913 (Box 1400, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Senior Party (Box 1400, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: Senior Reception (Box 1400, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Sophomore Reception, 1879 (Box 1400, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1883: Class Letters, 1912; 1915; 1918-20; 1923; 1925; 1929; 1935; 1940; 1944; 1951 (Box 1400, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1883: Songs (Box 1400, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1883: Class Supper (Box 1400, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1883: Group Photos (Box 1400, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1883: Seat, 1919-20; 1933 (Box 1400, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1883: Senior Dramatics, 1880 (Box 1400, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1883: Sundial, 1932-33 (Box 1400, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1883: "Weep" (Box 1400, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1883: Reunions (Photos), 1915; 1941; undated (Box 1401, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1889) (Box 1401, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1893) (Box 1401, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1898) (Box 1401, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1903) (Box 1401, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1908) (Box 1401, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1913) (Box 1401, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1923) (Box 1401, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1928) (Box 1401, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1933) (Box 1401, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1938) (Box 1401, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion (1943, 1948) (Box 1401, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1883: Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1401, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1883: Aldrich, Annette Howland (Photographs) (Box 1402, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel, 1882; 1938 (Box 1402, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Correspondence, Sept-Jan), 1879-80 (Box 1402, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Correspondence, Jan-Jun), 1880 (Box 1402, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Correspondence, Sept-Jan), 1880-81 (Box 1402, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Correspondence, Jan-Jun), 1881 (Box 1402, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Correspondence, Oct-Mar), 1881-82 (Box 1402, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Correspondence, Mar-May), 1882-83 (Box 1402, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Essays), 1881 (Box 1402, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Journal), 1879-82 (Box 1402, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Memorabilia), 1880-83 (Box 1402, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Allen, Mabel (Photographs), 1880-82 (Box 1402, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1883: Anthony, Mary Stuart (Box 1402, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1883: Anthony, Mary Stuart (Photographs), 1897; undated (Box 1402, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1883: Barrett, Minnie Lincoln (Photographs of Family, Northampton, Monson), 1899; undated (Box 1402, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1883: Bates, Emma (Box 1402, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1883: Bodman, Clara Philena, 1889; 1915; 1917; 1929; undated (Box 1402, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1883: Bodman, Clara Philena (Photographs), 1954; undated (Box 1402, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1883: Bowen, Julia Anna (Photographs, etc), 1880; undated (Box 1402, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1883: Brooks, Frona Marie, 1881; 1937; undated (Box 1402, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1883: Brooks, Frona Marie (Correspondence, Apr-Mar), 1880-83 (Box 1402, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1883: Brooks, Frona Marie (Correspondence, Undated College Years) (Box 1402, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1883: Brooks, Frona Marie (Photographs, etc), 1883-84; 1888; 1891; 1917; 1947; undated (Box 1402, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1883: Bush, Sally (Photographs) (Box 1402, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1883: Clark, Mary Annie, 1878; 1936 (Box 1403, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Converse, Clara Adra, 1902; 1923-24; 1929; 2003 (Box 1403, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Daniels, Susan Elizabeth, 1910; undated (Box 1403, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Dickinson, Eveline, 1927; undated (Box 1403, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Dickinson, Eveline (Album) (Box 1407.1)
  - Class of 1883: Dike, Florence Blanchard, 1919; 1923 (Box 1403, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Dunton, Ada Lamira (Box 1403, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Eames, Ella Florence, 1895; undated (Box 1403, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Edgarton, L., 1882-83; undated (Box 1403, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Fine, Jean Gurney, 1880; 1892; 1912; 1935 (Box 1403, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Flynt, Ella Eudocia, 1880; undated (Box 1403, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: Forman, Evelyn Jean, 1880-1883 (Box 1403, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Gifford, Alice Eliza (Box 1404, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Gilmore, Evelyn Langdon, 1956; undated (Box 1404, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Gleason, Clara Belle, 1939; 1947 (Box 1404, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Griswold, Louise Darling, 1882 (Box 1404, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Gulliver, Charlotte Chester, 1880; 1925; 1927 (Box 1404, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Gulliver, Charlotte Chester (Scholarship), 1927; 1929 (Box 1404, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Hall, Mira Hinsdale, 1932-33; 1937 (Box 1404, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Hall, Mira Hinsdale (Correspondence), 1879-1880 (Box 1404, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Hall, Mira Hinsdale (Correspondence), 1881-82; undated (Box 1404, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Haire, Anna Roberta (Box 1404, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: Hanna, Annie, 1997 (Box 1404, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Haring, Mary Elma (Box 1404, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1883: Harris, Clara Elizabeth (Box 1404, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1883: Harris, Henrietta, 1933 (Box 1404, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1883: Harris, Henrietta (Letters), 1881 (Box 1404, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1883: Harris, Henrietta Clark (Photo Album) (Box 1414.5)
  - Class of 1883: Harrison, Florence Marguerite (Box 1404, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1883: Henry, Esther Maria, 1879; undated (Box 1404, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1883: Hilliard, Caroline Elizabeth (Box 1404, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1883: Hine, Edith Caroline (Box 1404, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1883: Holmes, Esther Reynolds (Box 1404, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1883: Johnson, Elizabeth Frances, 1917; undated (Box 1404, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1883: Latimer, Mary Pelton (Photographs), 1880 (Box 1405, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Leach, Edith (Photographs), 1882-83 (Box 1405, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Leonard, Anne Louise (Photographs, etc.), 1928 (Box 1405, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Machado, Salomé Amelia, 1885; 1879 (Box 1405, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Machado, Salomé Amelia (Photographs), 1880-83; 1923; 1954 (Box 1405, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Marsh, Carrie Amelia (Letters), 1905-06; 1938; 1942 (Box 1405, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Marsh, Carrie Amelia (Photographs), 1882-83 (Box 1405, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Marvin, Anna Humphreys (Photographs), 1882; 1885 (Box 1405, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary H. Askew, 1881-83; 1886; 1968; undated (Box 1413, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary H. Askew (Journal), 1882-83 (Box 1413, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary H. Askew (Journal, Jan-June), 1882 (Box 1413, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary H. Askew (Journal, Sept-Dec), 1882 (Box 1413, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary Askew (Diaries and Operettas) (Box 1413.1)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary Askew (Memorabilia Books) (Box 1413.2)
  - Class of 1883: Mather, Mary Askew (Memorabilia Books) (Box 1413.2)
  - Class of 1883: Mead, Sara Elizabeth (Photographs), 1879-83 (Box 1406, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Letters), 1876-78; 1880-83; 1948-49 (Box 1414, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Correspondence to Family, Sept-Oct), 1877 (Box 1414, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Correspondence to Family, Nov-Dec), 1877 (Box 1414, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Correspondence to Family, Jan-June), 1878 (Box 1414, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Correspondence to Family, Sept-Nov), 1882 (Box 1414, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Correspondence to Family, Jan-June) (Box 1414, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Miller, Alice Mason (Photographs, etc.), 1882-83; 1895; 1932 (Box 1406, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Montgomery, Lizzie (Photographs), 1881 (Box 1406, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Morse, Anna Louisa (Photographs, etc.), 1938; 1979; undated (Box 1406, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Nordhoff, Amy Davis (Photographs) (Box 1406, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Osgood, Margarette Manton (Letters), 1879-83; 1887; 1938 (Box 1406, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Osgood, Margarette Manton(Photographs), 1882-83 (Box 1406, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Palmer, Clara Frances(Photographs, etc.), 1882-83; 1938 (Box 1406, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Palmes, Nannie Gertrude (Box 1406, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Parker, Julia F. (Photographs), 1882-83 (Box 1406, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: Parker, Mary (Photographs), undated (Box 1406, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Payne, Ella (Photographs) (Box 1406, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1883: Phillips, Maria (Photographs), undated (Box 1406, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1883: Poore, Harriet Paul (Photographs) (Box 1406, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1883: Rice, Mary Katrine (Photographs), 1880 (Box 1406, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1883: Robbins, Jane Elizabeth (Photographs, etc.), 1880; 1912; 1925; 1930; undated (Box 1406, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1883: Rogers, Sarah Philena (Photographs), 1880 (Box 1406, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1883: Scott, Jennie Louise (Photographs), 1879-80 (Box 1406, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1883: Smith, Clara Janet Augusta (Box 1406, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1883: Smith, Lucy Hannah (Photographs, etc.), 1898; 1942 (Box 1406, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1883: Snow, Florence (Photographs) (Box 1406, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1883: Snow, Florence (English Papers), 1890 (Box 1406, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1883: Stephens, Minnie Florence (Photographs, etc.), undated (Box 1406, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1883: Stetson, Ella Carleton (Photographs), 1881-82 (Box 1406, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1883: Story, Frances Rebecca (Photographs) (Box 1406, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1883: Taylor, Martha Skinner (Photographs, etc.), 1879-81; 1929; undated (Box 1407, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1883: Thaxter, Louise Godfrey (Photographs), 1882-83 (Box 1407, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1883: Tilden, Laura Bugbee (Photographs) (Box 1407, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1883: Tilton, Annie Eugenia (Photographs), 1882-83 (Box 1407, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1883: Van Ausdal, Mary (Photographs) (Box 1407, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1883: Waldron, Elizabeth (Photographs, etc.), 1880; 1928 (Box 1407, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1883: Ward, Alice (Photographs, etc.), 1906; undated (Box 1407, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1883: Ward, Alice (Publications), 1888; 1890-91; 1893; 1905; 1907; 1919 (Box 1407, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1883: Ward, Alice (Bailey) (Box 1414.2)
  - Class of 1883: Welles, Mary Crowell (Box 1407, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1883: Wheeler, Mabel Sarah (Photographs), 1881 (Box 1407, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1883: White, Mary Avery (Photographs, etc.), 1898; 1916 (Box 1407, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1883: Willard, Abby Gregory, 1879-80 (Box 1407, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1883: Willard, Abby Gregory, 1942 (Box 1407, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1883: Willard, Abby Gregory (Photographs, etc.), 1879; 1887; undated (Box 1407, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1883: Willard, Abby Gregory (Album) (Box 1414.3)
  - Class of 1883: Willard, Charlotte Richards, 1898-99; 1906-08; 1910; 1913-14; 1918; 1921 (Box 1407, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1883: Willard, Charlotte Richards (Photographs) (Box 1407, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1883: Williams, Cora May (Photographs, etc.), 1926 (Box 1407, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1883: Wilson, Flora Emeline (Photographs) (Box 1407, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1883: Wilson, Nellie Frances, 1880 (Box 1407, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1883: Winsor, Mary Pickard, undated (Box 1407, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1883: Wolcott, Clara Gertrude (Photographs, etc.), 1939 (Box 1407, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1883: Woodward, Ida Minette (Correspondence), 1880; 1882-83 (Box 1407, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1883: Woodward, Ida Minette (Photographs), 1890; 1933 (Box 1407, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1883: Woodward, Louise (Photographs) (Box 1407, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1883: Yale, Gertrude (Photographs) (Box 1407, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1883: Unidentified (Photo Album) (Box 1414.1)
  - Class of 1883: Unidentified (Photo Album) (Box 1414.3, Box 1414.4)
  - Class of 1883: Letters to alumnae, photos, news, 1883-1944; 2018-A-0021; 3 folders (2 legal folders, 1 envelope) (Box OV)
    Class of 1883 class letters to alumnae and other published material; photograph of Class of 1883 as first year students.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Donated by Susan Akers
    Akers, Susan
- Class of 1884 Records, 1876-1955; 4 boxes (2.75 linear feet)
  The Class of 1884 was the sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1884 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1884. Types of materials include black and white photographs, invitations, programs, letters, correspondence, diaries, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1884.
  - Class of 1884: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1415, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1884: Class Book (Box 1415, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1884: Commencement (Box 1415, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1884: Commencement Music (Box 1415, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1884: Commencement Speaker (Box 1415, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1884: Composite Photographs (Box 1415, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1884: Groups, 1882; 1887 (Box 1415, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1884: History, undated (Box 1415, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1884: Ivy Day, undated (Box 1415, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1884: Organization, 1880-89; 1891-94; 1898-99; 1904; 1906-35; 1937; 1941 (Box 1415, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1884: Reunions (Miscellaneous), undated (Box 1415, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1889) (Box 1415, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1894) (Box 1415, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1909) (Box 1415, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1914) (Box 1415, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1924) (Box 1415, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1925) (Box 1415, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1929) (Box 1415, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1934) (Box 1415, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion (1939) (Box 1415, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1884: Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1415, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1884: Senior Dramatics (Box 1415, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1884: Senior Reception (Box 1415, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1884: Songs, 1883-84; 1914; undated (Box 1415, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1884: Sophomore Reception, 1880 (Box 1415, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1884: Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1882 (Box 1415, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1884: Class Supper (Box 1415, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1884: Adams, Margaret, 1880 (Box 1416, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1884: Allis, Annie Amelia, 1895; 1897; 1944; undated (Box 1416, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1884: Allis, Fannie Augusta (Letters), 1881; 1917; 1931; 1936 (Box 1416, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1884: Allis, Fannie Augusta (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1884: Austin, Jennie Maude (Correspondence), 1882 (Box 1416, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1884: Austin, Jennie Maude (Photographs), 1883; undated (Box 1416, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1884: Barton, Mary Louisa (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1884: Brooks, Annie Smith (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1884: Bullen, Charlotte Packard, 1882 (Box 1416, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1884: Campbell, Mary B. (Photographs, etc), 1944; undated (Box 1416, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1884: Clark, Ella Cleveland, undated (Box 1416, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1884: Clough, Marion Belmont (Photographs, etc), 1885; undated (Box 1416, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1884: Connely, Bertha Lillian (Box 1416, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1884: Cox, Martha Lyman (Photographs, etc), 1936; undated (Box 1416, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1884: Crowell, Mary Savage (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1884: Delano, Sally Haskell (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1884: Duguid, Mary Evelyn (Box 1416, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1884: Duguid, Mary Evelyn (Photographs), 1880; 1882-84; undated (Box 1418, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1884: Duguid, Mary Evelyn (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1418)
  - Class of 1884: Dunn, Kate Clark (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1884: Dunn, Kate Clark (Album) (Box 1418.1)
  - Class of 1884: Fisk, Nina Perry (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1884: French, Clara (Photographs, etc), 1892; undated (Box 1416, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1884: Gladden, Alice (Correspondence), 1884-87; 1898; undated (Box 1416, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1884: Gladden, Alice (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1884: Herrick, Harriet Fidelia (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1884: Heywood, Lucy Florence, 1944; 1949; undated (Box 1416, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1884: Jameson, Katharine Strong (Photographs, etc), 1882-83; 1940; undated (Box 1416, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1884: Johnson, Mary Augusta (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1884: Kelsey, Louise Hoyt (Photographs), 1883-84; undated (Box 1416, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1884: King, Mary Emma (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1884: Lacey, Caroline Elvira (Photographs), 1876; 1880 (Box 1416, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1884: Martin (Irwin-Martin), Jeanne Clark (Photographs) (Box 1416, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1884: Mason, Mary Lyman (Diary), 1897 (Box 1416, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1884: Mason, Mary Lyman (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1416, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1884: Mead, Lydia Abigail (Correspondence) (Box 1416, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1884: Mead, Lydia Abigail (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1884: Mehan, Alida Mary (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 35)